nwc.com.au 2019-03-06

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
McMillan Shakespeare Group of Companies
Legal, Risk and Compliance

Privacy Policy
 Document Owner                 Group General Counsel
 Version Control                November 2015
 Approved by the Board          24 November 2015
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                       Page 2

Privacy Policy
Table of Contents
Table of Contents ............................................................................................................................................ 3
Privacy Policy .................................................................................................................................................. 4
1.     What is personal information? ............................................................................................................. 4
2.     Types of personal information we collect .......................................................................................... 4
3.     Why we collect your personal information ......................................................................................... 5
4.     How we collect your personal information ......................................................................................... 6
5.     Disclosing your personal information................................................................................................. 6
6.     What if we can’t collect your personal information? ......................................................................... 7
7.     Marketing our products and services to you ..................................................................................... 7
8.     Protection of your personal information ............................................................................................ 7
9.     Links ....................................................................................................................................................... 8
10.    Access to your information .................................................................................................................. 8
11.    What if the information is incorrect?................................................................................................... 8
12.    Cookies ................................................................................................................................................... 8
13.    Do we disclose your personal information to anyone outside Australia? ...................................... 9
14.    Complaints ............................................................................................................................................. 9
15.    Changes to this policy ........................................................................................................................ 11
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                                                                                                                               Page 3

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
McMillan Shakespeare Limited (MMS) and its related bodies corporate (McMillan Shakespeare Group) are
committed to protecting the privacy and the rights of individuals with whom it deals. This policy sets out how
we collect and manage personal information about those individuals and contains our privacy collection
statement. The McMillan Shakespeare Group includes:
        McMillan Shakespeare Limited ACN 107 233 983 (parent company)
        Maxxia Pty Ltd ACN 082 449 036
        Remuneration Services (QLD) Pty Ltd ACN 093 173 089
        Interleasing (Australia) Limited ACN 008 589 562
        TVPR Pty Ltd ACN 008 596 290 (trading as Holden Leasing)
        Maxxia Limited (NZ Company No. 2404936)
        Maxxia Fleet Limited (NZ Company No. 3571651)
        Maxxia (UK) Ltd (UK Company Number 8373870)
        Maxxia Finance Ltd (UK Company Number 8373926)
        Maxxia Limited (UK Company Number 7807901. Maxxia (UK) Ltd is a 50% share holder in this
         company)
        CLM Fleet Mgt Plc (UK Company Number 7473554)
        Presidian Holdings Pty Ltd ACN 603 801 770 (parent company of Presidian group)
        Davantage Group Pty Ltd ACN 161 967 166
        Franklin Finance Group Pty Ltd ACN 166 741 564
        Money Now Pty Ltd ACN 156 544 455
        National Finance Choice Pty Ltd ACN 156 544 464
        National Dealer Services Pty Ltd ACN 603 758 872
        Australian Dealer Insurance Pty Ltd ACN 158 647 271
        Motorsure Pty Ltd ACN 14 086 238 557
        Presidian Management Services Pty Ltd ACN 166 382 369
        National Insurance Choice Pty Ltd ACN 603 933 571
        United Financial Services Pty Ltd ACN 072 442 445
        United Financial Services Network Pty Ltd ACN 095 911 283
        United Financial Services (QLD) Pty Ltd ACN 073 887 813
We also have a Credit Information Policy that sets out how we handle credit information. For a copy of the
Credit Information Policy, please contact us. Our contact details are set out at the end of this policy.
1.     What is personal information?
Personal information is defined in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). Generally, it is information or an opinion from
which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained. This may include your name, address,
telephone number, email address, profession or occupation.
2.     Types of personal information we collect
The types of personal information we may collect include:
      name;
      address (residential and mailing address);
      contact details (telephone number, fax number and email address);
      age and date of birth;
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                                                                             Page 4

Privacy Policy
        employment details and financial information (your salary and the name and address of your
         employer);
        profession, occupation and job title; and
        employee number.
We may also collect the following information depending on the products and services we provide you:
      credit card details;
      bank account numbers;
      details of income, assets, liabilities, expenses, credit history, credit worthiness; and
      other information as required by the Anti-Money Laundering Counter-Terrorism Financing Act 2006
         (Cth).
Generally we do not collect sensitive information about you. Sensitive information includes your racial or
ethnic background, political opinions, membership of political, professional or trade associations or trade
unions, religious beliefs or affiliations, philosophical beliefs, sexual preferences or practices, criminal record
or health information. However, we may collect information about your memberships if required to provide
you with a specific product or service or where required by law.
When you visit our websites, we may collect statistics on the number, date and time of your visit, the number
of pages viewed and the manner in which you navigate through our sites.
When you call us, we may collect statistics on the number, date and time of your call and the manner in
which you navigated through our telephony system. We may also monitor and/or record in-coming and out-
going telephone calls for taxation, verification, substantiation and quality assurance purposes.
3.     Why we collect your personal information
We collect your personal information to perform our business activities and functions. We collect, hold, use
and disclose your personal information to provide you with products and services you have requested and for
the administration of those products and services.
We may also collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information to:
        conduct our business administration and operations (such as accounting, risk management, record
         keeping, statistical analysis, research, planning, systems development, testing and staff training);
        conduct our marketing (including direct marketing), planning, new product or service development,
         quality control and research;
        conduct customer satisfaction surveys / Net Promoter Score;
        answer your enquiries and respond to any complaints made by you;
        send you material about other products and services offered by us;
        assess and monitor the use and performance of our websites and provide you with access to secure
         areas of our websites;
        up-date our records and keep your contact detail updated; and
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                                                                                Page 5

Privacy Policy
         comply with any law, rule or regulation or request or direction from any regulator or governmental
          authority.
We may share personal information about you with our related bodies corporate, contractors and service
providers for any of the purposes outlined above.
4.     How we collect your personal information
Where it is reasonable and practical to do so, we will always collect personal information directly from you.
How we collect your personal information will depend on how you interact with us. For example, we may
collect it through your access and use of our websites, during your conversations with our representatives or
from application forms you complete.
There are occasions when we may need to collect your personal information from third parties, with or
without your direct involvement. Depending on the products or services you request or receive, the third
parties from whom we may collect personal information include your employer, market research
organisations, third party brokers and agents, credit reporting bodies, government agencies, your
representatives and your advisers and other organisations who, jointly with us, provide products or services
to you.
5.     Disclosing your personal information
We may disclose your personal information to another person or organisation. Depending upon the products
or service you have requested, we may disclose personal information about you to:
         your employer;
         our employees and related bodies corporate;
         our agents, contractors and service providers, including mail houses, web hosting providers, IT
          systems administrators or professional advisers such as accountants, solicitors, business advisers
          and consultants;
         regulatory bodies, government agencies and law enforcement bodies, including the Australian
          Taxation Office, CentreLink and the Department of Human Services;
         financial institutions, payment systems operators, credit reporting bodies or debt collection agencies
          in relation to the processing, administration and management of products and services requested by
          you;
         persons acting on your behalf, including your legal adviser, financial adviser, executor, administrator,
          trustee, guardian or attorney;
         insurers and reinsurers in relation to insurance products and services requested by you;
         superannuation funds in relation to the processing of contributions;
         other organisations or firms, who jointly with us, provide products or services to you;
         motor vehicle dealers in relation to the sourcing and remarketing of your motor vehicle;
         State and Territory road authorities in relation to motor vehicle registration and compulsory third
          party insurance;
         guarantors and prospective guarantors in relation to any applications for credit or lease applications
          made by you; and
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                                                                              Page 6

Privacy Policy
        fuel companies to enable those companies to properly record fuel purchases made by you.
In the unlikely event that the assets and operations of our business are sold to another party, our records of
personal information will be transferred to that party.
6.     What if we can’t collect your personal information?
If you do not provide us with the personal information described above, some or all of the following may
happen:
        we may be unable to provide the requested products or services to you, either to the same standard
         or at all;
        we may be unable to provide you with information about products and services you may want,
         including information about discounts, sales or special promotions; or
        we may be unable to tailor the content of our websites to your preferences and your experience of
         our websites may not be as enjoyable or useful.
7.     Marketing our products and services to you
We may use your personal information to offer you products or services we believe may be of interest to you
subject to our agreement with your employer. We may contact you by telephone, mail, SMS, fax or email.
You can notify us at any time if you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from us. Our
contact details are set out at the end of this policy.
We do not sell personal information to other organisations to allow them to do this.
8.     Protection of your personal information
We take reasonable steps to ensure your personal information is protected from misuse and loss and from
unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. We may hold your information in either electronic or hard
copy form. Personal information is destroyed or de-identified when no longer needed.
When browsing our web sites, you acknowledge that the internet is not always a secure environment and
that the computer and network you use contribute to the overall level of effective protection in place. You
further acknowledge that any transmission of information over the internet is out of our control before it
reaches our system. Only once we receive your transmission, we can take reasonable steps to ensure its
security.
In order to protect your personal information online, we ask that you observe the security requirements
relating to the protection of your user identification number and/or password used to access your online
account. We recommend that you:
      change your password on initial access to our website;
      ensure the user identification number given to you is kept securely;
      destroy any documentation (including any email) we issue containing your password;
      memorise your user identification number and password;
      do not tell anyone of your user identification number and password;
      immediately telephone us if you suspect your online account or related email account has been
         breached.
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                                                                            Page 7

Privacy Policy
9.     Links
Our websites may contain hyperlinks to other sites maintained by different organisations. We do not claim
any association with websites which are not clearly identified as our own and do not take any responsibility
for their content. Hyperlink users should observe such websites' terms of use, privacy policies and copyright,
which may or may not comply with the same privacy standards that we do.
10.    Access to your information
You may request access to any personal information we hold about you. The type of information you request
will determine the length of time we take to respond. We will generally respond using the same
communication method by which your request was originally made.
On occasion we will ask that you put your request in writing. This may include instances where you want
copies of material or access to archived information or if the nature of your application makes it necessary for
us to retain a record of your request.
You may be able to access some personal information via our customer service website. Access to personal
information via the customer service website requires the use of your unique user identification number and
password. No personal information is openly posted on the Internet. If you have difficulty finding the
information you want or in using the website, please contact us.
In some circumstances, we may charge an administration fee to retrieve your information, based on our
reasonable costs in providing the information to you. If we intend to charge an administration fee we will give
you an estimate of this fee so you can confirm you still want us to proceed with your request. We do not
impose any charge for submitting a request for access.
We are entitled to refuse you access to your information in certain circumstances. For example, you may not
be able to access personal information that would reveal personal information about another person, is
commercially sensitive material or we are prevented by law from disclosing. If this happens, we will provide
you with a reason for the refusal.
11.    What if the information is incorrect?
If you believe that personal information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or inaccurate, then you
may request that we amend it. We will generally correct the information upon request (or suggest alternative
arrangements for updating our records). If we do not agree that the information should be corrected, we will
provide you with a response stating the reasons.
12.    Cookies
We may collect personal information about you through the use of cookies. When you access our website,
we may send a “cookie” (which is a small summary file containing a unique ID number) to your computer.
This enables us to recognise your computer and greet you each time you visit our website without bothering
you with a request to register. It also enables us to keep track of products or services you view so that we
can send you news about those products or services. We also use cookies to measure traffic patterns, to
determine which areas of our website have been visited and to measure transaction patterns in the
aggregate. We use this to research our users’ habits so that we can improve our online products and
services. Our cookies do not collect personal information. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set
your browser so that your computer does not accept them.
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                                                                            Page 8

Privacy Policy
We may log IP addresses (that is, the electronic addresses of computers connected to the internet) to
analyse trends, administer the website, track users movements, and gather broad demographic information.
13.    Do we disclose your personal information to anyone outside Australia?
MMSG’s business activities are conducted in Australia and overseas. In order to provide our services to our
customers we may engage other Service Providers to perform certain functions. These functions may
involve the hosting or accessing of personal information which may also include credit information, by the
Service Provider outside Australia. At the present time MMSG’s Service Providers may disclose personal
information to the following countries: The United States of America, the Republic of Ireland and the
Philippines.
MMSG may also be subject to overseas corporate governance arrangements which mean that our overseas
service providers may be required to disclose certain personal information due to their own regulatory
obligations under foreign laws. In those instances, MMSG is not responsible for that disclosure.
14.    Complaints
If you have any questions regarding this policy or any concerns regarding our treatment of your personal
information, we invite you to contact us. Contact details are set out below.
We will aim to answer your questions or concerns in a timely and satisfactory manner. If we cannot resolve
the matter at the point of first contact, a representative will be in contact within a reasonable time to advise:
      who will be handling your enquiry; and
      how our investigations are progressing.
Our contact details are:
All customers:
Email:            privacy@mmsg.com.au
Mail:             The Privacy Officer
                  McMillan Shakespeare Ltd
                  Locked Bag 18, Collins Street East
                  Melbourne 8003
                  VIC, Australia
Phone:            1300 649 515
Facsimile:        1300 733 444
Maxxia (Australia) customers:
Website:          www.maxxia.com.au
Email:            privacy@maxxia.com.au
Mail:             The Privacy Officer
                  Maxxia Pty Ltd
                  Locked Bag 18, Collins Street East
                  Melbourne 8003
                  VIC, Australia
Phone:            1300 649 515
Facsimile:        1300 733 444
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                                                                              Page 9

Privacy Policy
Maxxia (NZ) customers:
Website:          www.maxxia.co.nz
Email:            privacyofficer@maxxia.co.nz
Mail:             The Privacy Officer
                  Maxxia
                  PO Box 7337, Wellesley Street,
                  Auckland 1141
Phone:            09 9030 622
Facsimile:        09 9030 623
RemServ customers:
Website:          www.remserv.com.au
Email:            privacy@remserv.com.au
Mail:             The Privacy Officer
                  Remuneration Services (QLD) Pty Ltd
                  Locked Bag 18, Collins Street East
                  Melbourne 8003
                  VIC, Australia
Phone:            1300 649 515
Facsimile:        1300 733 444
Interleasing customers:
Website:          www.interleasing.com.au
Email:            privacy@interleasing.com.au
Mail:             The Privacy Officer
                  Interleasing (Australia) Ltd
                  Locked Bag 18, Collins Street East
                  Melbourne 8003
                  VIC, Australia
Phone:            1300 649 515
Facsimile:        1300 733 444
Holden Leasing customers:
Website:          www.holdenleasing.com.au
Email:            privacy@holdenleasing.com.au
Mail:             The Privacy Officer
                  TVPR Pty Ltd t/a Holden Leasing
                  Locked Bag 18, Collins Street East
                  Melbourne 8003
                  VIC, Australia
Phone:            1300 649 515
Facsimile:        1300 733 444
Presidian Group customers:
Includes
Davantage Group Pty Ltd ACN 161 967 166
Franklin Finance Group Pty Ltd ACN 166 741 564
Money Now Pty Ltd ACN 156 544 455
National Finance Choice Pty Ltd ACN 156 544 464
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                       Page 10

Privacy Policy
National Dealer Services Pty Ltd ACN 603 758 872
Australian Dealer Insurance Pty Ltd ACN 158 647 271
Motorsure Pty Ltd ACN 14 086 238 557
Presidian Management Services Pty Ltd ACN 166 382 369
National Insurance Choice Pty Ltd ACN 603 933 571
Website:          http://www.presidiangroup.com/
Email:            privacy@mmsg.com.au
Mail:             The Privacy Officer
                  Locked Bag 18, Collins Street East
                  Melbourne 8003
                  VIC, Australia
Phone:            1300 649 515
Facsimile:        1300 733 444
United Financial Services customers:
Includes
United Financial Services Pty Ltd ACN 072 442 445
United Financial Services Network Pty Ltd ACN 095 911 283
United Financial Services (QLD) Pty Ltd ACN 073 887 813
Website:          http://www.unifin.com.au/ufs/index.aspx
Email:            privacy@mmsg.com.au
Mail:             The Privacy Officer
                  Locked Bag 18, Collins Street East
                  Melbourne 8003
                  VIC, Australia
Phone:            1300 649 515
Facsimile:        1300 733 444
15.    Changes to this policy
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting an updated version on this
website.
McMillan Shakespeare Group 2017                                                                        Page 11
